export const chapter = "Chapter - 5: The Cobra Mystery";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Who is playing ludo on the lawn?",
          optionA: "Ravi and Astha",
          optionB: "Mohan and Astha",
          optionC: "Gautami and Ravi",
          correctAnswer: "Ravi and Astha",
        },
        {
          question: "Why is Gautami happy in the text?",
          optionA: "Because she is on vacation",
          optionB: "Because her children are with her",
          optionC: "Because she found a cobra",
          correctAnswer: "Because her children are with her",
        },
        {
          question: "What did the cyclist inform Astha about?",
          optionA: "A lost wallet",
          optionB: "A snake in the lawn",
          optionC: "A new neighbor",
          correctAnswer: "A snake in the lawn",
        },
        {
          question: "How does Astha react upon hearing about the snake?",
          optionA: "Calm and composed",
          optionB: "Alarmed and horrified",
          optionC: "Excited and happy",
          correctAnswer: "Alarmed and horrified",
        },
        {
          question: "What is Mohan's job in the house?",
          optionA: "Playing with the kids",
          optionB: "Taking care of the lawn",
          optionC: "Cooking dinner",
          correctAnswer: "Taking care of the lawn",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What do Ravi and Gautami think about the number of snakebite deaths mentioned in the newspaper?",
          optionA: "They believe it's a huge number",
          optionB: "They think it's a small number",
          optionC: "They don't have an opinion",
          correctAnswer: "They believe it's a huge number",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why does Astha think the snake might have been sent by the Lord?",
          optionA: "As a reminder for her to visit Ujjain",
          optionB: "As a punishment for not working",
          optionC: "As a reward for their prayers",
          correctAnswer: "As a reminder for her to visit Ujjain",
        },
        {
          question: "What did the beggar woman offer to do to catch the snake?",
          optionA: "Pray to the Lord",
          optionB: "Call the police",
          optionC: "Send a snake-charmer",
          correctAnswer: "Send a snake-charmer",
        },
        {
          question: "How does the snake-charmer suggest catching the snake?",
          optionA: "With a net",
          optionB: "By playing a tune",
          optionC: "By using a stick",
          correctAnswer: "By playing a tune",
        },
        {
          question: "What happens at the end of the story regarding the snake?",
          optionA: "Mohan captures the snake",
          optionB: "The snake disappears through the gate",
          optionC: "The snake is found in a pitcher",
          correctAnswer: "The snake disappears through the gate",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Who is playing ludo on the lawn? Ravi and Astha are playing ludo on the lawn, while their mother Gautami is sitting on a chair nearby. At the far end of the lawn, Mohan is lying under the shade of a tree.",
          optionA: "Ravi and Astha",
          optionB: "Mohan and Astha",
          optionC: "Gautami and Ravi",
          correctAnswer: "Ravi and Astha",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Astha, go look what he wants. (walks to the gate) Yes, Uncle, what do you want? A big cobra has just got into your lawn. It crossed my wheel.",
          optionA: "Ravi",
          optionB: "Gautami",
          optionC: "Astha",
          correctAnswer: "Astha",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Astha (gasping in horror) That uncle said that he saw a cobra crawl into our lawn ... under the gate. (Everybody starts to look around in the grass and behind the hedges for the snake.)",
          optionA: "Ravi",
          optionB: "Mohan",
          optionC: "Astha",
          correctAnswer: "Astha",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ravi Don't worry, we'll find it out. (runs to where Mohan is sleeping) Uncle, Uncle ... get up, quick! There is a cobra. Mohan (squeezing his eyes in sunlight) How can a cobra come under the gate? It doesn't live on the road.",
          optionA: "Ravi",
          optionB: "Mohan",
          optionC: "Astha",
          correctAnswer: "Ravi",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Astha That thing is somewhere here. If it is not found out before evening, you are sure to be fired. Ravi He is the laziest servant I've ever seen.",
          optionA: "Astha",
          optionB: "Ravi",
          optionC: "Mohan",
          correctAnswer: "Ravi",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Astha Uncle, you're always making new excuses but you don't want to work. Look how tall the grass has grown. (Mohan finds a stick and starts beating about the bushes.)",
          optionA: "Ravi",
          optionB: "Astha",
          optionC: "Mohan",
          correctAnswer: "Astha",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ravi (carefully looking around) Having a cobra in the house is dangerous. I read in a newspaper recently nearly 30,000 people die of snakebite every year.",
          optionA: "Astha",
          optionB: "Gautami",
          optionC: "Ravi",
          correctAnswer: "Ravi",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Astha This cannot be true. 30,000 is a very large number. Newspapers don't publish anything what they want. They have data for each news story.",
          optionA: "Ravi",
          optionB: "Gautami",
          optionC: "Astha",
          correctAnswer: "Astha",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Gautami (spreading her hands heavenward) Forgive me, 0 Lord! I remember I promised to visit Mahakal at Ujjain, but couldn't go. This corona will not let me visit Ujjain. Lord must have sent that cobra as a reminder!",
          optionA: "Astha",
          optionB: "Ravi",
          optionC: "Gautami",
          correctAnswer: "Gautami",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ravi We can't go until this lockdown is over and trains resume.",
          optionA: "Astha",
          optionB: "Ravi",
          optionC: "Mohan",
          correctAnswer: "Ravi",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "The children are playing ludo on the lawn.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The cyclist informs Astha about a cobra entering the lawn.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Mohan was the one who found the cobra under the gate.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Astha believes that newspapers always publish accurate data.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ravi thinks that having a cobra in the house is not dangerous.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Gautami regrets not being able to visit Mahakal at Ujjain due to the lockdown.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The beggar woman suggests that the snake should be left alone in the lawn.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The snake-charmer is confident about quickly finding and catching the snake.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The snake-charmer recommends using a net to catch the snake.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The snake is eventually found and captured by Mohan.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
